Guide to the Dayton Company Advertising Scrapbooks, 1904-1968
The John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library Duke University Durham, N.C., USA
- Dayton Rochester, 1954-1968, (42 boxes)
  - Upstairs store, 1954-1968
    - 1957 Oct. 14-1958 Feb. 20 (Box 436)
    - 1958 Feb. 21-June 11 (Box 437)
    - 1958 June 12-Nov. 14 (Box 438)
    - [1958 Nov. 15-1959 Feb. 23] (Box [463])
      Box labeled out of sequence during processing; listed here for purposes of date range continuity.
    - 1959 Feb. 24-June 6 (Box 439)
    - 1959 June 8-Oct. 5 (Box 440)
    - 1959 Oct. 6-1960 Jan. 29 (Box 441)
    - 1960 Jan. 30-May 27 (Box 442)
    - 1960 May 30-Oct. 7 (Box 443)
    - 1960 Oct. 10-1961 Mar. 9 (Box 444)
    - 1961 Mar. 10-Sept. 9 (Box 445)
    - 1961 Sept. 11-1962 Feb. 8 (Box 446)
    - 1962 Feb. 9-Aug. 27 (Box 447)
    - 1962 Aug. 28-1963 Jan. 28 (Box 448)
    - 1963 Jan. 9-July 10 (Box 449)
    - 1963 Dec. 9-1964 May 20 (Box 450)
    - 1963 July 11-Dec. 9 (Box 451)
    - 1964 June 8-1965 Jan. 11 (Box 452)
    - 1965 Jan. 12-Sept. 30 (Box 453)
    - 1965 Sept. 30-1966 Mar. 25 (Box 454)
    - 1966 Mar. 28-Aug. 26 (Box 455)
    - 1966 Aug. 26-1967 Jan. 28 (Box 456)
    - 1967 Jan. 30-June 19 (Box 457)
    - 1967 June 20-Nov. 9 (Box 458)
    - 1967 Nov. 10-1968 Mar. 7 (Box 459)
    - 1968 Mar. 8-May 14 (Box 460)
    - 1968 May 15-Oct. 18 (Box 461)
    - 1968 Oct. 18-30 (Box 462)
    - 1958 Nov. 15-1959 Feb. 23 (Box 463)
- Dayton St. Paul, 1961-1968, (41 boxes)
  - Downstairs store, 1961-1968
    - 1961 July 31-1962 May 3 (Box 464)
    - 1962 May 4-1963 Mar. 4 (Box 465)
    - 1963 Mar. 5-Dec. 22 (Box 466)
    - 1963 Dec. 25-1964 Nov. 4 (Box 467)
    - 1964 Nov. 5-1965 Aug. 2 (Box 468)
    - 1965 Aug. 4-1966 Apr. 25 (Box 469)
    - 1966 Apr. 26-1967 Mar. 5 (Box 470)
    - 1967 Mar. 5-1968 Jan. 18 (Box 471)
    - 1968 Jan. 19-Nov. 3 (Box 472)
  - Upstairs store, 1961-1968
    - 1961 July 30-Oct. 19 (Box 473)
    - 1961 Oct. 19-Dec. 22 (Box 474)
    - 1961 Dec. 17-1962 Mar. 13 (Box 475)
    - 1962 Mar. 14-May 22 (Box 476)
    - 1962 May 23-Sept. 9 (Box 477)
    - 1962 Sept. 10-Nov. 11 (Box 478)
    - 1962 Nov. 12-1963 Jan. 30 (Box 479)
    - 1963 Jan. 30-Apr. 24 (Box 480)
    - 1963 Apr. 25-Aug. 5 (Box 481)
    - 1963 Aug. 6-Oct. 23 (Box 482)
    - 1963 Oct. 23-Dec. 24 (Box 483)
    - 1963 Dec. 25-1964 Mar. 18 (Box 484)
    - 1964 Mar. 19-June 2 (Box 485)
    - 1964 June 3-Sept. 13 (Box 486)
    - 1964 Sept. 14-Nov. 17 (Box 487)
    - 1964 Nov. 18-1965 Jan. 28 (Box 488)
    - 1965 Jan. 29-Apr. 11 (Box 489)
    - 1965 Apr. 12-June 17 (Box 490)
    - 1965 June 18-Sept. 15 (Box 491)
    - 1965 Sept. 16-Nov. 29 (Box 492)
    - 1965 Nov. 29-1966 May 16 (Box 493)
    - 1966 Feb. 17-Apr. 27 (Box 494)
    - 1966 Apr. 28-Aug. 8 (Box 495)
    - 1966 Aug. 8-Oct. 19 (Box 496)
    - 1966 Oct. 21-Dec. 23 (Box 497)
    - 1966 Dec. 23-1967 Apr. 2 (Box 498)
    - 1967 Apr. 2-June 9 (Box 499)
    - 1967 June 11-Oct. 1 (Box 500)
    - 1967 Oct. 2-Dec. 7 (Box 501)
    - 1967 Dec. 7-1968 Mar. 29 (Box 502)
    - 1968 Mar. 31-June 2 (Box 503)
    - 1968 June 2-Nov. 3 (Box 504)
- Dayton University Store, 1929-1953, (5 boxes)
  - 1929 Sept.-1932 May 14 (Box 505)
  - 1934 Sept. 26-1940 may 29 (Box 506)
  - 1940 May-1946 Sept. (Box 507)
  - 1946 Sept. 27-1948 Aug. 20 (Box 508)
  - 1948 Aug. 21-1953 Oct. 30 (Box 509)